麦克斯 我在垃圾白人窗这里
Max! Over here at our white trash window.
我需要你帮我看一下花洒
I need help with shower.
好了 栗宝 我们快要去上班了
All right, Chestnut we're heading for work, soon.
你知道规矩
You know the rules...
不许看成人电影 不许吃含糖零食
No R-rated movies, no sugary snacks
我希望你在11点就站好睡觉
and I want you standing up and asleep by 11.
什么问题
What's the problem?
我没办法打不开水[让它硬]
I can't turn it on.
解开你的浴巾 夸它的喷头很大
Well, drop your towel and tell it has a big nozzle.
你检查过老鼠了吗
Did you even do a rat check?
检查了 西尔多走了
Yes... Theodore is gone.
它都找到了比这里更好的公寓
Even he got a better apartment.
麦克斯 再提醒我一下
Max, remind me...
我们跟流浪汉不一样的地方在哪
what separates us from homeless people?
我们没有晒太阳的小麦色皮肤
We're not as tanned?
还有 我们有一个
Yeah, and we have a sometimes
时好时坏的花洒跟很赞的浴帘
functioning shower and that sweet shower curtain.
还是一名已经不需要他的"斗篷"的
Hmm, which was gifted to us by a homeless person
流浪汉送给我们的哦
who no longer needed his cape.
这样应该就好了
That should do it.
怎么声音停了
Hey, why'd the sound stop?
奇了怪了
That's weird.
好了 应该好了
All right. All right.
我成功让他"喷"了
Well, I got it turned on.
小家伙 你说啥
What's that, buddy?
凄凉得不能再凄凉了吗
It doesn't get any sadder?
哟哟哟 卡洛琳
Well, well, well, Caroline,
我都不知道今天是带"让你爽的男友"日呢
I didn't know it was "Bring your boyfriend to work" day.
厄尔 我们家连花洒都坏[破产]了
Even our shower head is broke, Earl.
我们被锈水喷了一身
We got blasted with rusty water
还有某些不明浓厚东西
and something thick.
我感觉自己好脏
I feel so dirty.
别嚎了 你都去苏菲与奥列格家洗澡过了
Stop. We showered at Sophie and Oleg's.
所以我才觉得自己"脏"
That's why I feel dirty.
浴室里有一只塑料小鸭 表情写着
There was a rubber ducky in there who looked like
"我看过太多不忍直视的变态事情"
he'd seen some really messed up stuff.
我们就像我们平常
Look, we will do what we always do
需要任何家用品或渔网紧身衣裤一样
when we need a new appliance or a fishnet body stocking.
问奥列格要
We'll ask Oleg.
有人说渔网紧身衣裤吗
Did somebody say fishnet body stocking?
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
我要开始绿化
I'm going green,
而且我不是指我的眼影画绿色
and I don't just mean my eye shadow.
是的 我要让我的身体开始备孕
Yup, I'm getting my body ready for pregnancy
所以要吃得健康与少吃烟熏肉类
with healthy eating and less smoked meats.
苏菲 我觉得绿化主要是指在环境方面
I think going green is more about the environment Sophie.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
那你有过几个孩子了呢 卡洛琳
And how many babies have you had, Caroline?
苏菲 我真希望我就是那胎儿
Sophie, I wish I were that fetus.
因为我好嫉妒
I'm jealous of anything that
任何能待在你"体内"长达九个月的物体
gets to be inside you for nine months.
奥列格 苏菲都要开始通过饮食净化身体了
You know, Oleg, since Sophie's doing a food cleanse,
你是不是也该"净化"一下你那张淫嘴
maybe you could do a cleanse for your potty mouth.
我喜欢这主意
I like that idea.
既然我为宝宝做改变 你也该做做
Since I'm changing for a baby, you should too.
从现在开始 你说的话必须得体
From now on, everything you say should be G-rated.
对 她说的可不是下"体"的体哦
Yeah, but the G doesn't stand for 'Gina.
所以我以后就只能乖乖上菜
So I'm supposed to serve bone-in rib eye and pulled pork
不能把某些菜名拿来开黄腔了吗
and not make any comparison to my junk?
我就在我的卡座吃健康的食品啦
Well, I'll be over here eating healthy in my booth.
麦克斯 我们家的淋浴坏了该怎么办
Max, what are we gonna do without a working shower?
我以后还能去哪里哭啊
Where will I cry?
我以后也不知道去哪里躲你了
And where will I hide from you?
姑娘们 如果你们需要洗澡
Girls, if you need a shower,
我新去的健身房里的设备很棒哦
there are wonderful facilities at my new gym.
那家健身房明显有托儿所啊
Well, they obviously have child care.
他们每天早上6点15分还会打来把我叫醒
They even give me a 6:15 wake-up call every morning,
好让我能准时去健身
so I can make it to my ideal body workout.
我现在也要把你从梦中叫醒
I'll give you a wake-up call right now.
你就多睡点吧
Sleep in.
就你那身 健到下辈子都没用
With that body, nothing's gonna work out.
我有两张"亲友"一天通票
Well, I have two "Friends and family" one-day passes
本来是要留给我爸妈来玩时 给他们用
that I've been saving for my parents' trip
可是上个月他们在泡菜国乱丢垃圾
but last month they littered in Korea,
结果坐牢来不了了
so they're in jail.
我在上面找到绿色食品了
Hey, I found something green on here.
麻烦来两份开心果冰激凌
Two pistachio ice creams, please.
苏菲 我不太...
Sophie, I'm not sure I...
臭三八 就给我上绿的东西就是了
Just bring me something green, bitch.
麦克斯 你在里面吗
Max, are you in here?
这里唯一一个姑娘已经在里面洗了很久了
Ah, only lady here has been in the shower a long time.
这不是你的吧
This isn't yours, is it?
不是 但我猜那也不是你的
Nope, and I'm guessing it's not yours either.
现在是了
It is now.
姐妹
Girl,
你为什么从来没告诉我淋浴可以这么舒服
why didn't you tell me a shower could be this good?
因为我觉得你不会相信我
I didn't think you'd believe me,
就像我告诉你有专门挂裤子的裤架子一样
like when I told you they make hangers just for pants.
这么久了 你一直都在里面洗吗
Have you been in there this whole time?
我中间出来撒过几次尿
I got out to pee a couple times.
也有几次没出来就在里面尿了
Then I didn't get out to pee a couple times.
在你第一次水乳交融的这段时间中
While you were meeting water for the first time,
我去上了三堂课
I took three classes.
帕伯的健美身材课
Body Rocket with Papo,
奈特的弹性韵律课与艾比的腹肌训练课
Flex Flow with Nat, and Ab Attack with Abby,
我还报名了奥布莱恩的凯尔特嘻哈舞蹈课
and I just signed up for Celtic Hip-Hop with Devandre O'Brien.
你能把这些塞进你的包里吗
Yo, can you fit these bad boys in your purse?
别忘了我的新帽子
And, uh, don't forget my new hat.
我会让我偷拿的擦手毛巾让个地儿
I'll make room for them next to the hand towels.
干得好 小妞
Ah, good for you, mami.
我就跟我家的保姆说
So I said to my nanny,
"就把她带去急诊室就好了啊
"Just take her to the emergency room.
我可不能错过布莱恩的健身课
I cannot miss my workout with Brian
就因为我女儿吃了一罐儿童黏土"
because Harlow ate a jar of Play-Doh."
仅供参考 浴室里有下体除毛膏
FYI, bottomless shaving cream in the shower.
我刚给自己弄了圣诞老人胡的造型
Gave myself a Santa beard.
你们好 我不是故意偷听
Hi, I wasn't listening in... all this tile,
但你们的声音真是声声入耳啊
your voices really carry.
谁是布莱恩
Who's Brian,
你们谈论这门了不起的课是什么
and what's this amazing class you're talking about?
与布莱恩一起YBBBB
YBBBB with Brian.
瑜伽屁屁芭蕾拳击超越健身
Yoga Booty Ballet Boxing and Beyond.
真是超越想象
And it's beyond.
哪个练习室 我要去
What studio is it in? I'll go.
麦克斯
Max?
这里没有麦克斯
There's no Max here!
一杯强腹免疫蔬果汁加香蕉
One Ab Blast Immune Boost with banana.
还有谁要点
Anyone else?
不好意思
Excuse me.
能给兄弟我来杯蜂花粉吗
Can a brother get some bee pollen?
谢谢 布莱恩
Thank you, Brian.
你确定你以前没上过
Are you sure you haven't taken
瑜伽屁屁芭蕾拳击超越健身吗
Yoga Booty Ballet Boxing and Beyond before?
因为你的屁屁好像天生就知道
'Cause it's like your booty just instinctively knew
怎么超越拉伸
how to go beyond.
你好 卡洛琳 你是布莱恩吧
Oh, hello, Caroline, and you're Brian.
我在墙上见过你的教练照片
I've seen your trainer photo on the wall.
我还以为你照片修过呢 看来没有啊
I guess it wasn't retouched as I assumed.
布莱恩 等等
Brian, wait up.
你忘了我们要拍30天的流汗纪念自拍照吗
Did you forget we're doing 30 days of sweaty selfies?
我能请你喝一杯果汁吗
Can I buy you a juice?
然后跟你亲热吗
And make out with you?
开玩笑啦 我可是结婚了
Joke, I'm kinda married.
是啊
Yeah.
卡洛琳 不如我为你创造一款果汁
Caroline, how about I create a juice for you
让你的健身效果达到最优
that will optimize your workout?
他给我们买过一杯果汁吗
Has he ever bought us a juice?
没 而我们给他买了一辆车
No, and we bought him a car.
席勒 给我来杯活力蔬果汁
Schiller, dude, give me a life boost.
席勒 我也要活力蔬果汁
Schiller, I'll have the life boost as well.
席勒
Schiller.
我念对了吗 席勒
Am I saying that right? Schiller.
你明天会来上课吗
Will you be in class tomorrow?
我想看你"飞"常灵活的屁屁
I'd love to see your flying lotus.
我的屁屁只有一天的通票
My lotus only has a one-day pass,
而且它不会飞
and it doesn't fly,
它得坐公车来
it takes the bus.
不再是了
Not anymore.
我给咱俩在果汁吧找了份工作
I got us jobs at the juice bar.
我们可以随心所欲上课洗澡了
We can take all the classes and showers we want.
我告诉他们我有榨汁[兴奋剂]经验
I told them I had juicing experience...
没撒谎哦 如果算上跟兰斯·阿姆斯特朗约会那周的话
not a lie if you count the week I dated Lance Armstrong.
厄尔 有一个洗澡间
Earl, this one shower,
水能从每个角度喷出来
the water comes at you from every angle,
而且绝不是下水道堵住所以乱喷
and not because sewage is backing up.
你的确看起来更快乐了 麦克斯
You do seem happier, Max.
你甚至还露出笑容
You're even kinda smiling.
你现在到底嗑到多嗨啊
How high are you right now?
不 我滴毒未沾
No, I am totally clean.
而且一尘不染哦
Literally.
洗过澡的麦克斯令人愉悦
Showered Max is a pleasure to be around.
而且她也没那么痒哦
Also, she's much less itchy.
我是型格健身房的会员
Hello, I'm a member of Physique Total Body.
刷卡 刷卡 刷卡
Swipe, swipe, swipe.
这地方不是谁都能进 太对我胃口了
I love belonging to a place where not everyone's allowed.
各位安安
Hey, everybody!
不 我不是健美狂人简·方达
No, it's not fitness nut Jane Fonda.
我是苏菲
It's Sophie Kuchenski!
我的一切都是健康又绿色
Yep, and everything about me is healthy and green.
苏菲 既然你现在提倡绿色排毒
Hey, Sophie, since you're being green,
我们给你带了一杯我们健身房的绿色蔬果汁
we brought you a Green Genie from our gym.
这么好啊
Oh, you did?
多谢了 卡洛琳
Uh, thanks a lot, Caroline.
我们不知道里面有什么
We don't really know what's in it.
在那里我们也对自己工作不在行
We're not good at our jobs there either.
瞧瞧 姑娘们 我真为她感到骄傲
Aw, look at that. I'm really proud of her, girls.
快吸进去 宝贝
Suck it down, baby,
我这话没有色色歧义哦
but not in a sexual way.
真是太美味了
This is delicious.
我超爱
I love it, yeah.
我太爱这杯蔬果汁了
I love this drink so much,
我要拿进洗手间
I'm gonna take it to the bathroom,
在里面好好爱它
and I'm gonna love it in there.
不要碰任何东西
Don't touch anything.
瞧 有钱老姐妹花来了
Hey, look. It's the Oldsen twins.
是你说我们在这里工作吗
Did you tell them we worked here?
我的餐厅制服从健身包掉出来
My diner uniform fell out of my gym bag,
她们不相信我是南斯加夫航空公司的空姐
and they didn't believe I was a stewardess on Air Yugoslavia.
健身伙伴们
Hey, gym buddies.
我们不用点餐 我们不吃东西
Oh, we don't need to order. We don't eat.
那你真是来对地方了
Well, you've come to the right place.
再次感谢让我转投布莱恩的课程
And thanks again for turning me on to Brian's class.
我很高兴你喜欢 但小乔
I'm glad you like it, but... Jodie?
你不能再去了
Yeah, you can't take it anymore.
所以...你懂的
So... yeah.
为什么不能
Why not?
布莱恩喜欢你
Brian likes you,
对此我们完全不理解
which we totally don't understand,
乔妹 你来说吧
but... Jodes?
好的
Yeah.
我们不想跟你分享他
We don't want to share him.
他是我们的全部
He's all we have.
所以
So...
你懂的
yeah.
你们俩都结婚生子了
You two are married with children.
没错 布莱恩就是我们的全部
Exactly. Brian is all we have.
我们能让你在健身房的日子很不好过
We can make it really uncomfortable for you at the gym,
人们已经开始议论你的打折瑜伽裤了
and people are already talking about your discount yoga pants.
所以 你懂的
So... yeah.
这里不仅仅只有你们俩能吓唬人
Oh, you're not the only person in here who can be threatening.
我去把我吓唬人的朋友找来
Let me go get my threatening friend.
麦克斯
Max.
给她们俩一个千刀万剐的眼神
Max, go over there and give them the dagger eyes.
就是阿憨看了会吓得抽搐那种
You know, the ones that gave Han the twitch.
是这个吗
This one?
是个屁啦
Uh, what is that?
不是
No.
那看起来像微笑
That's like a smile.
你从来不笑 少装了
You don't smile. Cut it out.
麦克斯 快点给她们脸色瞧瞧
Max, hurry, give them the face!
姐儿们 快看
Hey, ladies, look.
我们看不懂那是啥意思
We don't know what that means.
所以 你懂的
So... yeah.
干嘛 我尽力了
What? I'm trying,
但我猜洗过澡版麦克斯少了杀气
but I guess showered Max doesn't have it in her.
姑娘们 我这次就认了
Oh... you know I'll say this girls
但以后请别再提起
but don't quote me.
绿色排毒饮食不容易啊
It ain't easy being green.
姜在哪里
Now where's ginger?
姜在哪里啊
Where's ginger?
我不知道 跟盖里甘
I don't know, on that island
还有其他人在那座岛上吧
with Gilligan and the others?
她的瘦身奶昔呢
And where's her Slim Down Smoothie?
在搅拌机里 你能做完它吗
In the blender. Can you finish it?
这麦草的味道让我想吐
This wheatgrass smell makes me sick.
爷们点行吗
Well, man up.
老娘一人独挡三杯清肠汁
I'm balls deep in three gut busters over here.
天啊
Oh, God.
闻起来就像绿巨人的护阴裤
It smells like the Jolly Green Giant's jock strap.
老天 闻起来就像...
Oh, my God, it's like...
打住 你干呕害我也想干呕
Stop. You gagging makes me gag.
好了 快做好了
Okay, almost done.
瘦身奶昔
Slim Down Smoothie!
刚才没拿住
Kinda got away from me.
多出来的我不会收你钱
I won't charge you for the extra.
我点了里面要加香蕉的
Um, I wanted banana in this.
麦克斯 香蕉
Max, banana.
你想要香蕉 就给你香蕉
You wanted a banana. Banana.
席勒什么时候来换我的班啊
Where is Schiller to relieve me?
我该上YBBB课了
It's time for my YBBB class.
他的头发大概又被
He probably got his hair caught
卷腹机给卡住了吧
in the ab crunch machine again.
那个该死的卷腹机
That damn crunch machine.
好了 他来了 我走了
Okay, he's here. I'm out.
下课之后 你换我的班
After class, you relieve me.
不许磨磨蹭蹭
No dillydallying.
我用交通锥占了一间浴室
I got a hazard cone holding the shower
就是里面还有长凳的那间
with the railing and the bench in it.
耳环不错 拉克尔
Ooh, nice earrings, Raquel.
名牌珠宝
Oh, Pave Diamonds.
在一个储物柜发现的
Found them in a locker.
反正原来的主人也不需要
She doesn't need 'em.
你想要这个吗
Oh, you want this?
这是一个健身手环[乐队]
It's a fitness band.
在底下发现的
Found it on the floor...
储物柜的柜底
of a locker.
谢啦
Thanks.
唯一"上"过我身的乐队就是庞然大物组合
The only band that's ever been on me was They Might Be Giants.
他们的"下面"对不起团名啊
They were not.
美女 我刚听见那俩有钱老妈
Hey, mami, I just heard those two rich moms
在讲你朋友的坏话
trash-talking your friend.
告诉她别去上布莱恩的课了
Tell her to stay clear of Brian's class.
她们的老公是这家健身房的静默合伙人
Their husbands are silent partners in the gym,
在婚姻中也是"静默共枕人"
and also, in their marriages.
慢着 你是说我会失去我的淋浴吗
Wait, are you telling me I could lose my shower?
还有果蔬吧的工作
And your juice bar jobs.
对哦 还有那个
Oh, right, that whole thing too.
我得去阻止她
I gotta stop her.
感受此刻肌肉的拉伸
Feel that nice long stretch.
有事吗
Can I help you?
有人说里面有个地方湿嗒嗒 很危险
Uh... someone reported a dangerous, wet mess in here.
我没看见哪里湿嗒嗒的呀
I don't see a wet mess.
那你可能没看对地方
Then you're not looking right here.
走开 你打断我练功了
Go away. You're interrupting my flow.
很好 试着保持住 没错 卡洛琳
Good, now try and hold it. That's right, Caroline.
你能感受到吗
Okay, you feel that?
完美的大大的拉伸
Let's get a nice big stretch.
那真是够大的
That's big enough.
小姐 我们正在上课呢
Miss, we're in the middle of a class.
现在大家做婴儿式放松
And now let's all go into child's pose.
麦克斯
Max.
你不能再上这门课
You have got to get out of this class.
那俩老妈看你的眼神
Those moms are looking at you
像你把会胖的沙拉酱倒进她们的沙拉里
like you put dressing on their salad
还搅拌匀了一样
and mixed it in.
非常好 你的髋部比常人还放得开
Very good. Your hips are remarkably open.
多谢夸奖 布莱恩
Thank you, Brian.
我不能失去淋浴
I can't lose that shower.
我终于找到一件能让我爽的事情
I finally found something to make me feel good
而且跟大麻还不沾边
that doesn't end in "Arijuana."
小姐 你打断我们练功了
Miss, you're stopping our flow.
我刚也是这么说的 布莱恩
That's exactly what I said, Brian..
YBBBB是动态冥想
YBBBB is a moving meditation,
所以快动起来滚出去
so move it on out of here.
你干嘛这么逼逼逼逼个没完
Why you gotta BBBB so rude?
有礼了
Namaste.
还有你 "礼"他远点
And, you, Namaste away from him.
我回来了 瞧 啥事没有
I'm back. See? Nothing happened.
那俩妈啥也没做
Those two moms didn't do anything.
我是说 她们能有多危险啊
I mean, how dangerous can they be?
都是将近40岁的人了
They're almost 40
40岁 那不差不多50岁了吗
40? That's almost 50.
这节课真棒
Great class.
我感受到脂肪在燃烧
I felt quite the burn.
不如我请你们俩喝激情桃汁
How about I buy you ladies each a Sex on the Peach?
好啊 但不喝她做的
Great, just not from her.
阿憨 什么这么好笑
Han, what's so funny?
卡洛琳 有谣言说你上瑜伽课时"泄气"了
Caroline... rumor has it you let one fly in yoga class.
麦克斯 阿憨在说什么
Max, what's Han saying?
你噗了 你瓦斯外泄了
You tooted. Floated an air biscuit.
菊花漏气女
Pass-ah the gas-ah.
还需要我解释吗
Still need me to clarify?
好吧 各位 我澄清一下
Okay, hi, um, to be clear,
我没有做她们说的事 我绝对不会
I didn't do what they said. I wouldn't.
如果真有 我早就一头撞死在楼梯机上了
If I had, I would have already thrown myself down a StairMaster.
敢惹本宫
You mess with the bull,
本宫要你在屁里不得翻身
you get the fart rumor.
我勒个去 那俩60岁的老女人
Oh, my God, those 60-year-old women
居然造谣我放屁
started a fart rumor about me.
至少她们没让我们被炒鱿鱼
At least they didn't get us fired.
松一口气 这"气"不是讽刺你哦
Ah, phew. Ha, no pun intended.
布莱恩 刚才的课真棒
Hey, Brian, great class.
想帮我设计果汁吗
Wanna design a juice for me?
现在有点忙
Kinda busy right now.
有一个刚离婚的爸爸
I got a recently divorced dad looking to
想打造身材重回情场
get back out there in a big way.
再说 你放屁了
Plus, you farted.
真不敢相信会发生这种事
I can't believe this is happening.
我因为一件没做过的事在公共场合备受冷遇
I'm being shunned in public for something I didn't do.
我爸的庞氏骗局事件历史重演了
It's my father's Ponzi scheme all over again.
从今以后我成了 菊花漏气女卡洛琳
From now on, I'm Caroline, the gas-ah pass-ah.
我知道你被卷入臭屁漩涡中
Look, I know you're in a fart spiral,
但她们老公是这地方的股东
but their husbands own this place,
所以别做会毁了我们美好生活的傻事
so don't do anything to ruin this sweet situation for us.
抱歉 麦克斯
Sorry, Max,
但我以前从未因为她们对待我的态度
but I never told off those Upper East Side ladies
而骂过那些上东区的女人一句
for how they treated me five years ago,
所以我要通通还给这两位有钱婊
so I'm gonna have to let these two rich bitches have it.
别啊
Oh, no.
就因为你们的婚姻悲哀无爱...
Just because you're in sad, loveless marriage...
我们根本听不见你说什么
We couldn't even hear you,
所以...你懂的
so... yeah.
我很乐意复述每一个字
I'll be happy to repeat every word.
天啊
Oh, man.
我的手环掉进去了
My fitness band slid off!
我弄坏了超大榨汁机5000
I broke the Mega Juicer 5000.
你知道为什么叫它超大榨汁机5000吗
You know why they call it a Mega Juicer 5000?
因为它价值5000块
'Cause it costs 5000.
我们知道 我们买了一台给布莱恩
We know. We bought one for Brian.
我猜你们被解雇了 美女
I think you just got fired, mami.
给 分别礼物
Oh, here's a good-bye gift.
又一个健身手环
Another fitness band.
拉克尔 你能告诉那间有长凳的淋浴间
Raquel, will you tell the shower with the bench
我爱他吗
that I love him?
奥列格 里面进展如何
Oleg, how's it going in there?
我准备拧进去了
I'm ready to screw it in.
没有半点性暗示哦
Said with zero sexual innuendo.
给 我们真幸运
Here. How lucky are we that Raquel found
拉克尔在储物箱发现一个花洒头
this shower head in the locker?
我走回家消耗了515卡路里
I burned 515 calories walking home.
不对 那是时间
Oh, that's the time.
不许鄙视我
Still, nothing to sneeze at.
谁需要好健身房啊
Who needs a fancy gym?
奥列格现在在帮忙搞我们的洞
Oleg's here right now to take care of our hole.
好吧 你这句肯定是故意的
Okay, now you're doing it on purpose.
谁想跟我去喝一杯生菜汁
Anybody wanna go grab a lettuce wedge at Wedgies?
我的素食毒妈来了
There she is, my vegan vixen.
瞧瞧浑身散发出健康的光芒
Just look at that healthy glow.
糖
Sugar.
那不是光芒 是糖浆
That's not a glow. It's a glaze.
我吃了个甜甜圈
I had a doughnut.
它掉到我的脸上
Yeah, it fell on my face.
我必须得吃了 不然会窒息而亡
I had to eat it, or I would suffocate to death.
我最近都好好表现
I've been on my best behavior,
而你却没有"做"好你该"做"的事
and you're not holding up your end,
出于某种天杀的原因
which, for some godforsaken reason,
我还不能就这些词开黄腔
I'm not even allowed to comment on!
或许我们可以有个小作弊日
Oh, maybe we could have a cheat day,
择日不如撞日
and that day could be...
就今天吧
today?
磅蛋糕吗 知道我想"棒"打哪里吗
Pound cake? Know what I'd like to pound?
我当然知道
Oh, I sure do.
那还等什么
What are we waiting for?